The American Heritage® Dictionary of the English Language, Fourth Edition

Nunber of heawords/entries:	114764/105955

Version 1.0

Source: The American Heritage® Dictionary of the English Language, Fourth Edition on CD-ROM. Copyright (c) 2000 Houghton Mifflin Company.  Published by Houghton Mifflin Company. All rights reserved. Based on print version, The American Heritage(R) Dictionary of the English Language, Fourth Edition Copyright (c) 2000 by Houghton Mifflin Company. Published by Houghton Mifflin Company.

The American Heritage® Dictionary of the English Language, Fourth Edition on CD-ROM is a comprehensive electronic dictionary with all the features of its print counterpart and more.  This outstanding reference CD has a wealth of definitions, including over 10,000 new ones, etymologies, usage notes, and other word features. It also includes over 1,000 color photographs, illustrations, and maps, and nearly 70,000 spoken pronunciations.

The Dictionary is cross-referenced to The American Heritage® Dictionary of Indo-European and Semitic Roots Supplement ("AHD Indo-European and Semitic Roots Supplement (En-En)").

For further information on the Dictionary and the list of the included additional articles see the entry "_AHD4: 0. CONTENTS".
